OK, I'm going to give Gary in this segment a lob serve, a series of lob serves.
Now the lob serve is much tougher to return if it's executed well cause the ball is coming at a very steep angle.
So it's much harder to hit a ball coming like that then it is one coming like that.
So watch what he does, how he handles this ball.
It's going to take a lot more, he's got to use his ears, he's got to hear how solidly it's hitting the wall and he's also got to determine if it's going to come off the back wall, cause if it's not going to come off the back wall you got to get it while it's in the air so let's see how he does.
OK, he's taking my fine lob serve as if it's nothing.
That's pretty good.
But the beauty of a good lob serve for the server is I'm going to have time to get over there to cover his shot.
Good, that's very good.
So you see how Gary has to be very patient cause it's very hard to hit a kill shot off this serve.